{
    "_id" : ObjectId("555b7292ffe4585c23e35a97"),
    "organization" : ObjectId("55531b1fd5a6540e1113a771"),
    "title" : "Complete survey",
    "type" : "Manager Survey",
    "createdAt" : ISODate("2015-05-19T17:27:46.246Z"),
    "totalParticipants" : 0,
    "confirmed" : false,
    "questions" : [ 
        {
            "question" : "Select the resources most important to your groupâ€™s getting their job done [ressource]",
            "type" : "items_rank",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e9"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What are the top 3 teams with which your team interacts on a regular basis? [department]",
            "type" : "department",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e8"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What are the items you receive from {tag_department_repeat_3} ?",
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e7"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : true
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "How frequently are you expecting {tag_ressource_repeat_3} from {tag_department_repeat_3} ?",
            "type" : "unique_choice",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e2"),
            "responses" : [ 
                {
                    "response" : "Weekly",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e6")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Monthly",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e5")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Quarterly",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e4")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Less often",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e3")
                }
            ],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : true
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "How frequently are they sharing {tag_ressource_repeat_3} from {tag_department_repeat_3} ?",
            "type" : "unique_choice",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698dd"),
            "responses" : [ 
                {
                    "response" : "Weekly",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e1")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Monthly",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698e0")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Quarterly",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698df")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Less often",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698de")
                }
            ],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : true
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "Are you receiving {tag_ressource_repeat_3} from {tag_department_repeat_3} on time for your purposes?",
            "type" : "unique_choice",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d8"),
            "responses" : [ 
                {
                    "response" : "Rarely",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698dc")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Sometimes",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698db")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Often",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698da")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Always",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d9")
                }
            ],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : true
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What is the level of quality of {tag_ressource_repeat_3} from {tag_department_repeat_3} ?",
            "type" : "unique_choice",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d4"),
            "responses" : [ 
                {
                    "response" : "Minimal quality",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d7")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Acceptable quality",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d6")
                }, 
                {
                    "response" : "Excellent quality",
                    "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d5")
                }
            ],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : true
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What do you give to {tag_department_repeat_3} ?",
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698d3"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : false,
            "generic" : true
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What are the items you receive from {department_1} ?",
            "tag" : "department",
            "tagOrder" : 1,
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698ea"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : true,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What are the items you receive from {department_2} ?",
            "tag" : "department",
            "tagOrder" : 2,
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698eb"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : true,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What are the items you receive from {department_3} ?",
            "tag" : "department",
            "tagOrder" : 3,
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698ec"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : true,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What do you give to {department_1} ?",
            "tag" : "department",
            "tagOrder" : 1,
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698ed"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : true,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What do you give to {department_2} ?",
            "tag" : "department",
            "tagOrder" : 2,
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698ee"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : true,
            "generic" : false
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "What do you give to {department_3} ?",
            "tag" : "department",
            "tagOrder" : 3,
            "type" : "items_multiple_choices",
            "_id" : ObjectId("555c8b83a756cfd3179698ef"),
            "responses" : [],
            "genericParent" : true,
            "generic" : false
        }
    ],
    "__v" : 45
}